I'd like to warn you that this video is very sad.
It's so sad that not even the Cat March will cheer you up.
This space colony is called The Sad Colony.
You'd think it's a bad name choice but it's actually because the colony was created by Richard Sad.
A man that was eaten by cannibals...
...while attempting to eat a cannibal.
The faction that ran this colony was called
"The Even Sadder Faction."
That's just inexcusable.
Theodor's birthday was in two days.
They had to get food for his celebration...
...so they sent out their two hunters
to kill innocent, homeless animals.
One hunter was named "Danny Goodpersn."
A father of five that volunteered at a Kitten Hospital.
Today, he died.
Bitten by some kind of animal...
...thus creating 5 brand new orphans.
What bit him?
The zoologist, Dr.Furry... ary, went to find out.
A new planet comes with dangerous animals.
And the worst one of them all
was the POISONOUS Yorkshire Terrier
That also bit Dr.Furryary
And made him sick.
I am well aware that makes it a venomous Yorkshire Terrier...
...and that's what made it so deadly.
It was both.
Dr.Furryary would die unless someone
could bring him the only cure.
The problem was that it was guarded.
By Nine Panthers,
Six Polar Bears,
and one very angry
By Nine Panthers,
Six Polar Bears,
and one very angry Tortoise.
The other hunter: BadassMcGee went for it.
He had hope.
But this is the wrong story for delusion.
The second he got there...
...he was hit by a train.
The cure wasn't even necessary
because Dr.Furryary was fine.
It might just have been a normal Terrier.
Or it was a miracle...
...because the odds of surviving
the Yorkshire venom was 1 in 960000
The exact same yearly odds as
getting struck by Lightning.
(uh oh)
A thunderstorm was brewing that would destroy the generators and kill the crops.
Mark was an electrician...
...that was deadly afraid of electricity...
...after being tortured by it on his 9th Birthday.
The torture was a present from his Step-Mom.
Saving the generators, there would be
a 90% chance he would be electricuted.
But... he faced his fears and fixed them.
And then they exploded...
And so did the crops.
Now they had no vegetables and no meat.
A new hunter could fix this.
Danjel was the only choice.
The problem was...
...he was blind.
He wasn't born that way...
He lost one eye in a car accident
where he also lost one parent.
Then another eye and another parent
in another car accident.
Between then and now, Danjel lost 14 more guardians in car accidents.
And he never inherited anything.
...because he lost his lawyer in a...
Yeah, you know how.
But people needed food, and he had a rifle.
Danjel decided to challenge himself, and hunt...
HUMANS.
So he went to the neighbor(ing) village...
...but he couldn't see anything
so he just shot at random.
Then he heard their screaming voices...
It was his parents.
They hadn't died, they just abandoned him.
Because he was fucking crazy.
And then he was lynched.
Everyone mourned their lynched sociopath.
There's no way this could get any sadder, unless
There's no way this could get any sadder, unless someone had crippling alcoholism.
Like Nicole.
But her addiction didn't end there.
First it was the Devil's Hooch.
Then the Devil's Lettuce.
Then Luciferium.
Eventually, she was addicted to every drug in the game.
And it had only been 10 minutes.
SHE BEAT HER ADDICTION,
and was on her way to recovery.
She was back again, then she died.
Of a heart attack.
(Apparent Character Break)
I tried to kill her with an overdose,
but I don't know how to...
(Apparent Character Break)
And currently, it says she had
a heart attack in her Right Pinky, that's not right, but-
It is sad.
How could the people of the
colony deal with all this sadness?
Tania jogged.
She was also a Fast Walker.
A kicker, and had several other traits related to her legs.
So it was so devastating that today...
...she would step on a land mine...
...causing her right leg to have a
...causing her right leg to have a heart attack.
I still haven't-
She was now useless...
...and the only thing she could do was to go in
...and the only thing she could do was to
go into A MURDEROUS RAGE.
Nothing is sadder than a
crippled woman attempting murder.
The odds of everyone surviving seemed impossible...
Just like the odds of you ever owning a house.
Two people left, so what about a ceremony?
Weddings are always a happy affair.
Like that one time in Game of Thrones
when he finally got those traitors.
Before reaching the altar...
...an army of raiders called the "Wedding Crashers" attacked...
...and were all immediately killed by a bunch of turrets.
Hooray!
No.
They were only like this because
they grew up in a bad environment.
All of them had abusive parents.
One of the raiders had real talent for playing the violin.
That's what you are hearing right now.
One turret also (?) caught fire and that
spread all over and to the colony.
King couldn't handle the thing she loved the most getting burned.
So she ran into the fire and died.
What was the thing she loved?
It was Hope.
Hope.
Vibrating Hope.
The storm came and calmed down the flames.
Theodor was alone.
He could risk it and travel to another colony....
...or he could try to rebuild.
He reentered the house and...
SURPRISE!
Everyone was fine!
It was all just an elaborate ruse for a fun surprise party.
This-
This- these are the hallucinations
of a cold and starving man.